[ Balls Clacking ]
On the side.
You didn't do that
on purpose.
Otherwise that would have
been a great shot.
Watch this. Side pocket.
Holy shit!
What?
"Christopher Murray,
a teacher at
St. Vincent's Elementary,
has been accused
of sexually abusing
two former students."
St. Vincent's? That's that
school you went to, right, Mac?
Yeah, me and Charlie.
What else does it say?
"Murray has been the physical
education teacher and boys'
basketball coach for 25 years."
Blah, blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah, blah.
Ah. "The accusers are
two brothers whose names
are being withheld,
"but the investigation
will focus on
the mid-1980s...
"as the time period
for alleged abuse.
The police are hoping
more young men
will come forward."
- Wow. That's horrible.
- Did this guy teach you guys?
Yeah.
No.
Yes, he did.
We were in the same class.
No. Yeah. Well, no,
I didn't like it though.
What the hell
are you talking about?
I didn't like that class.
What?
I gotta go!
Holy shit.
Charlie got molested.
When dealing with molestation,
the first step is always
understanding.
So we need to take a moment
and assess the situation.
Write this down.
What? No, look. First of all,
we can't sit around
and let him wallow in it.
And second of all, the
first step is acknowledgment.
So I better write that down.
No. No, no.
Whoa! What, guys--
What the hell are you guys
talking about?
Sweet Dee and I
took psychology at Penn,
so let the grown-ups talk.
Okay? Thank you.
Okay?
[ Dee ]
Listen. I think we need
to have an intervention.
You know, bring
his friends and family
together for support.
Yeah,
that's a good idea.
Let's tell everybody
Charlie knows that he got
blown by a gym teacher.
Then we'll throw him
a little surprise party,
celebrate the occasion.
Okay, you know what?
You being a smart-ass--
not helping Charlie.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Who said anything
about getting blown?
The article didn't specify
what type of abuse it was.
It could have been anything.
Yeah, but do you think
he got blown?
I don't know.
Yeah, you know?
Probably got blown.
Which is why I think
you need to reconsider
my idea.
Okay. You know what?
Stop. I'm sorry. We need
to clarify something here.
Do you think that Murray
blew these guys?
Why are you so obsessed
with the blowing aspect
of all this?
Because I knew these two
brothers that the article
was talking about.
The McPoyle twins--
Ryan and Liam. Okay?
They were the type of kids
that would blow snot bubbles
and rub 'em over each other.
They were gross,
and they smelled like
a couple of unwiped assholes.
So what?
Well, if Murray is, like,
fondling or touching them,
whatever--
I get it, all right?
But if he's dishing out
blow jobs, come on.
- I just don't understand.
- What do you not get?
- What are you talking about?
- You're not getting this?
I was in that class
with them, all right?
I was with those guys!
- Um, are you okay, dude?
- No, dude. I'm not okay.
How come you're
getting so upset?
The police are asking
for more young men
to come forward.
That means there are
more guys out there
who've been blown.
What are you looking for?
Photographs.
I have photographs.
Oh, my God. You have
photographs of it?
Oh! Okay.
Listen, are you trying to say
that you got molested?
Okay, look at this.
Look at this guy, huh?
I was cute.
I was energetic.
I was fun.
I mean, what exactly
was this prick looking for?
What are you--
Sorry?
If the McPoyles got blown
and Charlie got blown,
then why didn't I
get blown?
You're goin' to hell,
dude.
Seriously.
[ Knocking ]
Yo! McPoyle!
Hey, open up!
Hey, Charlie.
Long time no see.
What do you want?
Is your brother here, man?
I gotta talk to you guys.
Yeah?
Yeah!
Can I come in?
Yeah.
Come on, man.
I need to talk to you guys.
Go. Move. Go.
Go. Come on.
I'm not gonna walk
in front of you! Go.
Just come in.
No, you go first,
and I will follow you.
Shut the door.
I will shut the door.
Whoa. That was
really weird.
Yeah.
Well, this confirms it.
He definitely got molested.
Ugh. We gotta
get in there.
Get-- We gotta
get in there?
Yes.
You can't just thrust yourself
in the position of caregiver
like that.
"Caregiver"?
Why are you throwing
around big words?
I actually majored
in psych, so--
You failed all your classes.
So?
I had a minor,
and I passed all mine.
Well, you know what?
Three-quarters of a major is
bigger than a whole minor.
I don't even know how
to respond to that.
That doesn't surprise me.
Well, it shouldn't
because what you said
is really dumb, you know.
That's a good one.
Yeah, it is.
That was good.
I liked that one.
I felt good about it.
♪♪ [ Country Instrumental
On Stereo ]
So did you want
a beverage of some kind?
No! Where's your brother?
We just stepped
out of the shower.
He'll be down in a minute.
Listen, you guys can't go--
Did you just say "we"?
What?
Did you just say,
"We just stepped out
of the shower"?
I said "he."
Right. Okay.
Listen. I heard about
the Coach Murray thing.
You guys cannot go
to the police and say
that he molested you.
Why not?
Because he didn't
molest you!
That's true,
but he's a dick,
and we hated him.
This is our chance
for revenge. You want in?
No!
[ Man ]
I think you do.
Hello, Charlie.
Hello, Ryan.
I don't know if you've
been paying attention
to the news recently,
but there are millions
to be made here, my friend.
Oh, sure, there's
the classic route
of priest molestation,
but we thought
we'd mix it up a bit.
We're going after
the whole damn
school board.
If you want in on the team,
we could probably get a nice
class-action suit going.
Okay. Okay, first of all,
there are people out there
who actually have been molested.
And you guys
are gonna exploit that
for your own personal gain?
You assholes are securing
your place in hell.
-We thought about it.
We're willing to roll the dice.
-I won't let you do it.
I'm gonna call the cops.
Oh, no, you won't,
Charlie.
Oh, yes, I will.
Oh, my friend,
I'm afraid not.
And why not?
We'll tell the cops the
whole thing was your idea.
We should tell the cops
that that fat dickhead
gym teacher...
we had in junior high
molested us...
and just sue the shit
out of him!
[ Laughing ]
I-- I was joking.
Really?
I'm not joking though.
I'm not joking. I'm really not.
I wouldn't even joke
about something like that.
We should do it.
I wanna do it.
Shit.
We'd hate to have to
put this whole thing
on your shoulders.
Shit.
So you're gonna have to
keep your mouth shut.
You don't have to join us,
but if anyone asks you
point-blank,
[ Whispers ]
your ass got molested.
Otherwise, we're talking
conspiracy charges.
And prison
can be a bad place...
for someone like you,
Charlie.
A very bad place.
[ Spraying ]
Soon as Charlie comes out,
we gotta grab him,
take him back to the bar,
get him liquored up
and tell him, "We know
you got molested."
Gonna have to disagree
with you, Sis.
I think we need to
ease him into it.
There he is.
Okay, you know what?
Dr. Gainer used to say that
in situations like this--
Dr. Gainer?
That guy was an idiot.
He was not.
Yes, he was.
Talk about molesters.
That guy--
He didn't molest me.
I had sex with him
'cause I wanted to.
You had sex with Dr. Gainer?
Of course I did.
No, you had--
Oh!
He was a hot older man.
Gross!
Okay. You know what?
You have no room to talk.
All the girls you've molested.
Whoa, whoa. Don't start
throwing that word around
like it's meaningless, okay?
This is serious.
Fine.
Great.
Molester.
[ Sighs ]
[ Rings ]
[ Exhales ]
Hey, Coach Murray!
Yeah?
It's me-- Mac!
I don't know what this shit
is all about.
One day the cops
just roll into my classroom
and they haul me out of there.
And they did it right
in front of my kids too.
Yeah. Totally.
Molestation?
I mean, please!
I got so much ass
back in those days.
What the hell did I need
that kind of shit for?
God, man, I hear you.
So much ass, it was like--
Whew.
Oh, and you know what,
to tell you the truth?
I don't even remember
who these assholes are
that are accusing me.
Nothing special there,
right?
I guess.
Nothing special. You know,
Coach, I've been working out
a lot since grammar school.
Good for you, son.
Yeah, it's good
for you, right?
You know when you get
real tight, like, right up
in here in this area here?
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
Not here.
Like right in here.
What are you doing?
What do you want me to do?
All right. I-- Okay.
[ Exhales ]
Oh!
That's a good shot, bud.
Hey, tell me something, man.
What's been going on
with you lately?
You just seem--
You know, um,
I'm just distracted.
Is that why you ran out
of the bar the other day?
No. No. I was--
I had some stuff
I needed to do.
It just popped in my head.
Yeah, well,
that's understandable.
We've all got things
that we have to do.
Yeah.
What you running
from, Charlie?
What?
Dee, could you
grab me a beer?
Grab one yourself.
I'm right in the middle
of a game.
Your game isn't working.
Let me play now.
Let me play the game
the way I want to play it.
Your way is dumb,
and it's not working.
Then we'll play your game.
It's not gonna get
the results we want.
You're playing
a game for children,
and it's not working.
Charlie's not a baby.
Charlie!
Great. Nice.
Good job, Dennis.
Great.
How are you gonna
put this on me?
You messed it up!
We have to push him!
Push him?
You're pushing him away.
Now he knows something's up.
Good.
Good?
Guys,
I have good news!
I've been reading up
on the subject of pedophilia.
It turns out that it isn't
about sex after all.
It's about power.
So, the assailant doesn't
go after the one he finds
most attractive-- this guy.
He goes after
the weakest he can find.
Wow. That is good news.
- Jesus, Mac.
What is wrong with you?
- No. You're not following.
If Murray was looking for
the weakest he could find,
it wouldn't have been Charlie.
[ Dee ] Why not?
Because Charlie was
a bit of a psychopath.
When he got excited,
his face would turn purple
and he'd start biting things.
I don't think Murray
would've put his dick
anywhere near him.
- What about
the McPoyle brothers?
- They were prime real estate.
I'm sure he went
to town on them.
What's your point?
Charlie didn't get molested.
[ Chuckling ]
What?
Good.
I'm sure he didn't.
Oh, boy.
Yeah.
Leave this to the two people
that are qualified to deal
with the situation.
It is cute
that you did some research
and got four books though.
Nice work.
Yeah, good job.
You know what?
We tried it your little
tippy-toe pussy way.
That failed miserably.
So now why don't we try
something that will work?
Look, I just want to say
that I think this is
a terrible approach.
You know how
I already know that?
'Cause you keep saying it.
I keep saying it
because... it is.
I'm sorry
you're wrong about stuff
all the time.
I'm sorry that you're
sorry all the time.
What?
That doesn't make
any sense.
I don't care.
Well, hello, Dennis!
Hi, Mrs. Kelly.
Don't you look
so handsome!
And, Dee, so beautiful.
Thank you, Mrs. Kelly.
I'm sorry we had to stop by
like this, but we really need
to talk to you about something.
What?
It's about Charlie.
[ Bawling ]
Oh, I can't believe this!
I just can't believe it!
Though I have to admit,
it does explain
a lot about him.
Yes, we were thinking
the same thing.
Yes. Oh. Be strong, Bonnie.
Be strong for your little
gingerbread man.
Now is not the time
for an episode.
[ Shaky Breathing ]
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine!
[ Panting ]
So, what do you need
from me?
Hello? Ma?
In here, Charlie!
Hey, I got your message.
You sounded kinda funny.
Come on back, honey.
Is everything all right?
Hello, Charlie.
Mom?
Grandma? Uncle Jack?
What's-- What's everybody
doing here?
Well, we've all gathered here
at the request of your friends.
Hey, bud.
Hi, Charlie.
Hello, Charles.
I-- I don't exactly know
how one of these things
are supposed to go.
But we understand
that there's been
some abuse.
These two boys
have been strong enough
to admit what happened,
and we thank you
for that.
Just hope that
that man goes away
for a long, long time.
Prison can be a bad place
for a guy like that.
Very bad place.
Now, we're not exactly sure
how this thing
is supposed to go.
But your friends
have been helping us out...
on a couple of key points.
Now?
Okay, Charlie,
show us on the doll.
Show you what?
- Where he touched you.
- Oh, yeah.
[ Mouths Words ]
Shall I turn it over?
Yeah, turn her over.
Do it.
Slow. Slow.
♪♪ [ Radio: Hawaiian ]
I think that went well.
You did a wonderful job,
Charlie.
I really think
they bought it.
Oh, yeah. Definitely.
I gotta say, my favorite part
was at the end there
when we were all hugging,
and my sister screamed
and told everyone that
I touched her vagina.
Yeah!
So, Charlie,
where to?
Oh, well, I was thinking
we should, uh, zip down
to the police station,
file an official report.
I gotta do it
sometime, right?
That's the spirit.
Let's get it
on the books.
[ Clears Throat ]
Excuse me. I'd like to, uh,
speak to a detective, please.
Name?
Charlie Kelly.
And what is this
in reference to?
Sodomy.
Okay. Uh, take a seat.
Someone will be
right with you.
You're doing
the right thing, Charlie.
The American school system's
been oppressing people
for years.
It's about time we start
doing a little oppressing
ourselves.
That doesn't make sense.
Yes, it does.
How are we oppressing
anything? You need to
think before you speak.
You do.
Charlie Kelly?
Oh. That's me.
Uh, I'll be right back.
Have a good time.
Twenty-five million
is a lot of clams.
Split it 50-50.
Charlie's gonna
want something.
- How 'bout Charlie?
- [ Inaudible ]
Yeah.
He'll want some.
He's not gonna
get some.
We could always split it
50-50-50.
You even hear
what you're saying?
Your gums
are bleeding.
How'd it go?
Great.
I just ratted you out.
Can I see you two boys
for a minute, please?
So you're not gonna get
in any trouble at all?
Uh, no. No, not really.
And since the McPoyles
are gonna plead guilty,
I'm off the hook completely.
That's great.
Sorry. Was he saying that
the intervention worked?
No, I don't think
that's what he's saying.
What are you talking about?
It was the final push
Charlie needed.
Turns out three-quarters
of a major--
not so bad after all.
And the best part of it,
actually, for me now
is the fact...
that everybody thinks
that I've been molested.
So, in a way,
my life is ruined.
In the meantime,
I'm gonna go in the back office
and cry and cry and cry...
and drink for a while.
[ Door Closes ]
Emotional release.
Another giant step forward.
My God, we're good.
Doctor.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, so I just want
to apologize again
for the other day.
It's all right, Mac.
Don't worry about it.
Awkward, right?
You know what? You were
a good student at school.
You got potential.
Just put that
in your pocket.
Really? You mean that?
I mean that.
Great, Coach. That's all
I really needed to hear.
Good.
That is so great for me.
Hey, say hi
to those folks for me.
I will. Thanks.
All right.
That little prick's
goin' to hell.
[ Voices Speaking Backwards ]